[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of dead life form does E.T. revive in the 1982 science fiction movie E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial directed by Steven Spielberg?", "correct_answer": "A dead flower", "incorrect_answers": ["A dead mouse", "A cut tomato", "A dead fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of herbivorous animals are the granivores?", "correct_answer": "Animals that feed on seeds", "incorrect_answers": ["Animals that feed on buds", "All of these", "Animals that feed on fruit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1941 movie The Maltese Falcon, starring Humphrey Bogart, is based on the novel of the same name by this author.", "correct_answer": "Dashiell Hammett", "incorrect_answers": ["Raymond Chandler", "Edgar Wallace", "James M. Cain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rhode Island, the smallest US State, also has the shortest state motto. What is this one-word motto?", "correct_answer": "Hope", "incorrect_answers": ["Union", "Freedom", "Courage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed the T-1000 android in the 1991 movie Terminator 2: Judgment Day, directed by James Cameron?", "correct_answer": "Robert Patrick", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Biehn", "Arnold Schwarzenegger", "Edward Furlong"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is transplanted during the medical procedure xenotransplantation?", "correct_answer": "Tissues from one species to another", "incorrect_answers": ["Organs from one person to another", "Blood from one person to another", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Americium?", "correct_answer": "Am", "incorrect_answers": ["Ag", "Au", "Ac"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is soil pollution one of the biggest threats to earthworms?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why is everybody teasing Mr. Johnson, one of the convicts in the 2003 comedy The Fighting Temptations?", "correct_answer": "Because of his very high voice.", "incorrect_answers": ["Because of his very small stature.", "Because he sings falsely, but he considers himself a great vocalist.", "Because of his ridiculous hairstyle."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed Thomas Edward Lawrence in the 1962 movie Lawrence of Arabia?", "correct_answer": "Peter OToole", "incorrect_answers": ["Alec Guinness", "Anthony Quinn", "Omar Sharif"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the budget for the movie The Shawshank Redemption?", "correct_answer": "$ 25,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$3,000,000", "$ 100,000", "$ 10,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What foe does the expedition in Journey to the Center of the Earth face along the way?", "correct_answer": "Count Saknussen", "incorrect_answers": ["Father Green", "Colonel Sato", "Doctor Van Pelt"]}]